export const quizQuestions_19 = {
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Which CSS property can set the font style to italic?",
          choices: ["font-weight", "font-family", "font-style", "font-size"],
          correctAnswer: "font-style"
        },
        {
          question: "Which property is used to adjust the space between text characters?",
          choices: ["letter-spacing", "text-align", "line-height", "margin"],
          correctAnswer: "letter-spacing"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the default font-weight for <p> paragraph text in most browsers?",
          choices: ["bold", "normal", "light", "bolder"],
          correctAnswer: "normal"
        },
        {
          question: "What CSS property is used to set the color of text?",
          choices: ["color", "font-color", "text-color", "background-color"],
          correctAnswer: "color"
        },
        {
          question: "Which CSS property would you use to capitalize all text in a heading?",
          choices: ["text-transform", "text-align", "font-style", "text-capital"],
          correctAnswer: "text-transform"
        },
        {
          question: "How do you specify the font size in web design?",
          choices: ["px", "em", "rem", "Any of the above"],
          correctAnswer: "Any of the above"
        },
        {
          question: "Which font family is often easier to read for long paragraphs of text?",
          choices: ["serif", "sans-serif", "cursive", "monospace"],
          correctAnswer: "serif"
        },
        {
          question: "The line-height property sets the spacing between what?",
          choices: ["Characters", "Words", "Lines of text", "Paragraphs"],
          correctAnswer: "Lines of text"
        },
        {
          question: "What does the text-align property justify?",
          choices: ["Vertical alignment", "Horizontal text alignment", "Letter-spacing", "Line-height"],
          correctAnswer: "Horizontal text alignment"
        },
        {
          question: "Which property controls the space between an element and other elements around it?",
          choices: ["padding", "margin", "border", "spacing"],
          correctAnswer: "margin"
        },
      ],
    };
  